# ZURA DOGHANADZE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER



**5**98 11 64 84

zuradoghanadze@gmail.com

Q Georgia-Tbilisi

## SKILLS

- HTML/CSS
- Git/Github
- Figma/XD adobe
- JAVASCRIPT
- Linux

#### PROFILE

I am Zura Doghanadze. I am 23 years old. I have been interested in logical thinking and algorithms since childhood, that's why after graduating from university I decided to study programming due to its scale.

The result exceeded expectations and it turned out that being a frontend developer is exactly what I enjoy doing.

I am motivated and purposeful. I want to study and develop this profession better.

#### If you are interested in my projects:

**Github -** https://github.com/zura-doganadze

**Linkedin-** https://www.linkedin.com/feed/

#### EDUCATION

#### ILIA STATE UNIVERSITY

2018 - 2022

Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, Business Administration and Management, General

### EXPERIENCE

**UNILAB COURSE** 

HTML, CSS, JS

2022-2023

RE:EDUCATE

re:start programming

2022-2023

#### LANGUAGES

- Georgian Native
- English Professional Working Proficiency